<HINTS>
    <HINT>You can go fishing at the Fishing Hole. Click on Fishy Joe at the bait shop to purchase a fishing pole.</HINT>
    <HINT>You can buy clothes from the Clothing Co. store located on East Market Street.</HINT>
	<HINT>You can purchase Dragon Mounts from Flame in Pawthorne Forest.</HINT>
    <HINT>You can view another panda's player card by clicking on them and selecting the panda face icon above their head.</HINT>
    <HINT>The backpack icon in the lower right corner will open your backpack.</HINT>
    <HINT>You can play mini-games by clicking the joystick icon on the menubar and clicking on the game you want to play.</HINT>
    <HINT>Some Project Pandanda residents like Paige in Bear Hollow have minigames for you to play.</HINT>
    <HINT>Click on the Discord icon on the menu bar to join our Discord Server.</HINT>
    <HINT>You can make coins by selling the items you've collected. To sell your items you will have to locate the various vendors who will buy them.</HINT>
    <HINT>If you want other Pandas to visit your tree house, you'll need to unlock it first. Travel to your tree house and click the key icon. You'll see it change to a key with an open door.</HINT>
    <HINT>Mr. Elmhurst in West Market Street will buy your old furniture from you.</HINT>
    <HINT>Paige in Bear Hollow sells fun potions.</HINT>
    <HINT>If another panda is bothering you, you can report them to a staff member in our Discord Server!</HINT>
    <HINT>You should report a panda if you see them breaking any of the Project Pandanda Rules. To report a player join our Discord Server and contact a staff member!</HINT>
    <HINT>If the game is running real slowly you can make it run faster by changing the "Graphics Quality" setting in your options. The options menu can be accessed by clicking on the "Options" icon on the menu bar.</HINT>
    <HINT>You can customize the border color around the game from the options menu. The options menu can be accessed by clicking on the "Options" icon on the menu bar.</HINT>
    <HINT>You can make your panda go to sleep by typing a "z" on your keyboard. </HINT>
    <HINT>You can make your panda jump by typing a "j" on your keyboard. </HINT>
    <HINT>You can make your panda dance by typing a "d" on your keyboard. </HINT>
    <HINT>You can make your panda sit by typing a "s" on your keyboard. </HINT>
</HINTS>